Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 10 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1421
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1941-1947 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Lynn Gunther to James Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation and Strike Organization, August 1, 1941; 1.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation and Sheet Metal Products Strike, August 13, 1941; 2.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Sheet Metal Products Contract and Robert Hadley Negotiation, August 29, 1941; 3.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Strike and National Labor Relations Board, September 3, 1941; 4.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Cannon Organization and Hadley Negotiation, September 5, 1941; 5.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Thrifty Sheet Metal Contract, September 5, 1941; 6.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding California Sheet Metal Contract, September 8, 1941; 7.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees Inter-union Rivalry, September 11, 1941; 8.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Primetal Specialties & Vimcar Steel White Collar Workers, October 15, 1941; 9.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Western Insulated Wire Contract, November 6, 1941; 10.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Greyhound Automotive Grievance and Organization, November 10, 1941; 11.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Military Contracts Productivity, November 10, 1941; 12.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Fischer Corporation, November 17, 1941; 13.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Commerical Welding Negotiation, December 30, 1941; 14.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Sheet Metal Strike, January 8, 1942; 15.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Vimcar Contract, January 13, 1942; 16.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Reliable Manufacturing Strike, March 16, 1942; 17.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding Allied Ohnograph, Pryne, and Comcoel Negotiation, March 26, 1942; 18.
      - Gunther to Frank Knox Regarding Dura Steel and Military Contract, May 20, 1947; 19.
      - Gunther to Knox Regarding Military Contracts and Reliable Manufacturing, May 20, 1942; 20.
      - Gunther to Knox Regarding Vim Car Street Sosh and Military Contracts, May 20, 1942; 21.
      - Gunther to Matles Regarding War Labor Board and Unemployment, May 21, 1942; 22.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1954 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Martha Hard to Julius Emspak Regarding Decca Negotiation, December 9, 1943; 1.
      - Hard to Sidney Gilbert Regarding Decca Contract, February 4, 1944; 2.
      - Hard to Emspak Regarding Sentner Visit, February 28, 1944; 3.
      - Hard to William Sentner Regarding Political Action and Factionalism, May 17, 1944; 4.
      - Hard to Livingston Regarding Union Security, October 12, 1944; 5.
      - Hard to Sentner Regarding Membership Drive, Staff Members, and Organization, June 14, 1945; 6.
      - Hard to Sentner Regarding Staff Members, July 27, 1945; 7.
      - Hard to Lewis Schwellenbach Regarding US Motors Negotiation, October 25, 1945; 8.
      - Hard to William Cahn Regarding US Motors Negotiation and US Motors Milford Organization, October 31, 1945; 9.
      - Hard to Emspak Regarding US Motors Negotiation, November 20, 1945; 10.
      - Hard to Ben Riskin Regarding Veterans and General Cable Contract, June 19, 1946; 11.
      - C. Hartford to UE Regarding Jensen Strike, October 12, 1953; 12.
      - Hartford to UE Regarding Dura Steel Strike, February 15, 1954; 13.
      - Robert Hooker to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Political Action, April 21, 1945; 14.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1946 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - W.G. Hornbostel to James Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, September 9, 1937; 1.
      - Hornbostel to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, September 16, 1937; 2.
      - Hornbostel to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Negotiations, November 3, 1937; 3.
      - Hornbostel to Emspak Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, November 9, 1937; 4.
      - Hornbostel to Emspak Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation and Factionalism, April 1938; 5.
      - Hornbostel to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation and Factionalism, April 1938; 6.
      - Hornbostel to W.E. Murphy Regarding Factionalism, August 17, 1938; 7.
      - Hornbostel to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 1939; 8.
      - Roberta Jones to Louis Pine Regarding GE Strike, March 28, 1946; 9.
      - Jones to Emspak Regarding Westinghouse and US Motors Strike, Separate Charters, and Amalgamation, April 8, 1946; 10.
      - Jones to Emspak Regarding US Motors Strike, May 20, 1946; 11.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Helio Kennedy to Local 902 Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, October 10, 1938; 1.
      - Kennedy to Local 902 Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, November 1, 1938; 2.
      - Kennedy to Julius Emspak Regarding Maytag Strike, November 2, 1938; 3.
      - Kennedy to Emspak Regarding Officers, June 15, 1939; 4.
      - Kennedy to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 16, 1939; 5.
      - Kennedy to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 21, 1939; 6.
      - Kennedy to James Matles Regarding Star Lighting and Vimcar Contract, August 9, 1939; 7.
      - Kennedy to Matles Regarding Grayson Organization, August 24, 1939; 8.
      - Kennedy to Emspak Regarding GE Contract and Organization, November 21, 1939; 9.
      - Robert Kennedy to Matles Regarding Columbia Negotiation with April 1941, Press Release, March 31, 1941; 10.
      - Robert Kennedy to Emspak Regarding Columbia Record Strike, 1941; 11.
      - Robert Kennedy to Matles Regarding Columbia Record Strike, 1941; 12.
      - W.H. Lassley to Matles Regarding Western Insulated Wire Negotiation and Wages, September 11, 1942; 13.
      - Ceclia Lewis Regarding Servel Boycott, February 13, 1941; 14.
      - Lewis to Matles Regarding Pryne and Allied Phonograph Contract, April 16, 1941; 15.
      - Lewis to Matles Regarding Organization with Membership, May 9, 1941; 16.
      - Lewis to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, May 24, 1944; 17.
      - Frank Lopez to Matles Regarding Political Action, December 12, 1940; 18.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1949 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - James Marsh to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, January 15, 1949; 1.
      - Joe Marty to Julius Emspak Regarding AFC Inter-union Rivalry, June 10, 1942; 2.
      - Marty to Matles Regarding Contracts and Negotiations, August 31, 1943; 3.
      - Marty to Emspak Regarding Domestic Manufacturing and Domestic Thermostat Wages, November 2, 1945; 4.
      - Dan Razzaia to Matles Regarding Record Industry Negotiation, November 3, 1939; 5.
      - Razzaia to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 18, 1940; 6.
      - R.E. Reeder to Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, June 18, 1938; 7.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Organization, July 7, 1938; 8.
      - Reeder to UE News Regarding Fischer and UE News, January 9, 1939; 9.
      - Reeder to James Carey Regarding Government Contracts, August 11, 1939; 10.
      - Reeder to Emspak Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, September 16, 1939; 11.
      - Reeder to Carey Regarding National Labor Relations Board, September 21, 1939; 12.
      - Reeder to Emspak Regarding NLRB, September 21, 1939; 13.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding NLRB, September 21, 1939; 14.
      - Reeder to Emspak Regarding CIO Convention, September 24, 1939; 15.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Firings and Columbia Recording, October 15, 1939; 16.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Columbia Records Negotiation and Columbia White Collar Organization, October 17, 1939; 17.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Factionalism and Joint Council, October 19, 1939; 18.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Joint Council and Factionalism, October 27, 1939; 19.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Joint Council, November 1, 1939; 20.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Joint Council and Fischer Contract, November 5, 1939; 21.
      - Reeder to Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 8, 1939; 22.
      - Reeder to Emspak Regarding Officers, December 16, 1939; 23.
      - Reeder to Emspak Regarding Officers, April 24, 1940; 24.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1955 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Myron Rhamy to Julius Emspak Regarding Columbia Recording Strike, April 12, 1941; 1.
      - A.D. Ross to Emspak Regarding GE Los Angeles Contract, June 9, 1940; 2.
      - Ross to Emspak Regarding GE Wages, June 11, 1941; 3.
      - Samuel Salzman to Emspak Regarding Dura Steel Unemployment, May 28, 1940; 4.
      - Frank Spector to Edward Matthews Regarding Officers, October 30, 1944; 5.
      - Spector to Emspak Regarding Officers and Constitution, February 13, 1945; 6.
      - Spector to Emspak Regarding Union Membership, February 23, 1945; 7.
      - Spector to David Scribner Regarding War Labor Board and Hadley Case, September 5, 1945; 8.
      - Arnold Awift to UE Regarding Pryne Strike, October 3, 1951; 9.
      - F. Temple to James Matles Regarding Grayson Organization and Factionalism, August 22, 1939; 10.
      - Temple to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 17, 1939; 11.
      - Del Tucker to Martha Hard Regarding General Cable, Wages, and Veterans, June 10, 1946; 12.
      - Tucker to Phillip Murray Regarding Factionalism and Congress of Industrial Organizations, April 28, 1949; 13.
      - Tucker to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Square D Negotiation, March 20, 1950; 14.
      - Tucker to Emspak Regarding Emspak Trial, May 26, 1955; 15.
      - Lloyd Van Dycke to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Foreign Policy, January 2, 1945; 16.
      - Van Dycke to Emspak Regarding Los Angeles Organization, December 17, 1945; 17.
      - Van Dycke to Matles Regarding Twentieth Century Record Organization, August 20, 1946; 18.
      - Van Dycke to Matles Regarding Keynote Record Negotiation, December 24, 1946; 19.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Gertrude Weiss to Julius Emspak Regarding Los Angeles Visit, October 11, 1939; 1.
      - Michael Weiss Regarding GE Service Organization, December 6, 1939; 2.
      - Weiss to GE Employees Regarding GE Oakland Organization, December 15, 1939; 3.
      - Weiss to James Matles Regarding GE Service Organization and Grievances, January 18, 1940; 4.
      - Weiss to Matles Regarding GE Service Wages, March 28, 1940; 5.
      - Weiss to Matles Regarding GE Negotiation, March 28, 1940; 6.
      - Weiss to Matles Regarding Publicity, April 24, 1940; 7.
      - Weiss to Matles Regarding Organization, April 24, 1940; 8.
      - Weiss to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action, May 28, 1940; 9.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding Civil Liberties, June 14, 1940; 10.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding Grievances, July 23, 1940; 11.
      - Weiss to Matles Regarding GE Grievances, October 21, 1940; 12.
      - Weiss to Matles Regarding GE Negotiation and Officers with Election Results, January 22, 1941; 13.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Service White Collar Organization, March 1941; 14.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Negotiation, March 3, 1941; 15.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Negotiation, April 14, 1941; 16.
      - Weiss to Simpson Regarding GE Grievances, April 29, 1941; 17.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Organization, June 6, 1941; 18.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Negotiation, June 9, 1941; 19.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding Conscription, December 20, 1941; 20.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Grievances, March 7, 1942; 21.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding Red Cross, April 10, 1942; 22.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding Wages and GE Grievances, August 17, 1942; 23.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Grievances, October 6, 1942; 24.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding Productivity and GE Grievances, October 15, 1942; 25.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Grievances, October 17, 1942; 26.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Overtime, October 19, 1942; 27.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Membership, February 5, 1943; 28.
      - Weiss to Emspak Regarding GE Membership, May 17, 1943; 29.
      - Weiss to Joseph Dermody Regarding GE Seniority, April 27, 1944; 30.
      - Executive Board to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, August 14, 1946; 31.
    - Local 1421 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937-April 1954 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Local 1421 Report of Financial Secretary, April-December 1937 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Local 1421 Per Capita Reports, May 1937-July 1940 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Local 1421 Finances, 1939-1953 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Joint Council Expenses, September 1939; 1.
      - Projected Expenses, 1939; 2.
      - Office Expenses, March 21, 1949; 3.
      - A:2 Tube Benders Strike, December 8, 1952; 4.
      - Del Trucker General Cable Expenses, December 1953; 5.
    - Local 1421 UE Livewire, September-November 22, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Local 1421 Local 1421 Organizer, May-August 1941 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Local 1421 Newspapers, 1939-1942 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1421 News, July 25, 1939; 1.
      - Cannon News, June 8, 1942; 2.
    - Local 1421 Leaflets, 1938-1951, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - "Victory" Regarding Dura Steel Strike, August 15, 1938; 1.
      - "Dura Workers" Regarding Organization, September 8, 1938; 2.
      - "Jitter Fest" Regarding Local Dance, September 8, 1938; 3.
      - "Grayson Employees" Regarding Grayson Organization, September 13, 1938; 4.
      - "Wear Your Asbestos Shoes" Regarding Local Dance, September 1938; 5.
      - "A Letter" Regarding General Cable Los Angeles Organization, June 10, 1942; 6.
      - "Westinghouse Meeting" Regarding Westinghouse Organization, June 10, 1942; 7.
      - "Uncle Sam Didn't Freeze Wages", June 12, 1942; 8.
      - "Strong Unions Needed in War Time" Regarding General Cable Organization, June 25, 1942; 9.
      - "UE Position on Piecework" Regarding US Motors Piece Work Organization, June 26, 1942; 10.
      - "Open the Door, Johnny" Regarding Capitol Records Lockout, 1947; 11.
      - "Let's Look at the Record" Regarding Pryne Strike, June 15, 1951; 12.
      - 'Move Facts For the Record" Pryne Strike, June 20, 1951; 13.
      - "Pryne Has Plans For You" Regarding Pryne Strike, June 22, 1951; 14.
      - "You May Be Next" Regarding Pryne Negotiation, 1951; 15.
      - "A Message" Regarding Pryne Negotiation, 1951; 16.
      - "We Support YOU" Regarding Pryne Negotiation, June 27, 1951; 17.
      - "Strike Bulletin" Regarding Pryne Strike, July 2, 1951; 18.
      - "Come to the Family Picket Line" Regarding Pryne Strike, July 3, 1951; 19.
      - "Strike Bulletin" Regarding Pryne, July 5, 1951; 20.
      - "Support Our Strike" Regarding Pryne, 1951; 21.
      - "Capitol Records Unfair" Regarding Capitol Records Lockout, n.d.; 22.
      - "Hitler Did It Too" Regarding Allied Negotiation, n.d.; 23.
      - "Why Star Lighting" Regarding Star Lighting Lockout, n.d.; 24.
    - Local 1421 Pamphlets, 1942-1945 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Harry Bridges Answers James Cannon Regarding Negotiations, May 12, 1942; 1.
      - Calling Regarding US Motors, October 30, 1945; 2.
    - Local 1421 Newspaper Clippings, 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - "CIO Disc Strike Threat Hits Entire Columbia Organization", April 21, 1941; 1.
      - "Columbia Record Strike Continues", April 28, 1941; 2.
      - "L.A. County Communist Registration Ordinances Are Held Unconstitutional", October 7, 1950; 3.
    - Local 1421 Press Releases, 1940, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Press Release Regarding Columbia Recording Contract, March 11, 1940; 1.
      - Press Release Regarding Fischer Contract, n.d.; 2.
      - Press Release Regarding Fischer Strike, n.d.; 3.
    - Local 1421 Organization and Per Capita, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Louis Fabian to James Carey, June 15, 1937; 1.
      - Fabian to Julius Emspak, June 19, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to Fabian, July 6, 1937; 3.
    - Local 1421 Wage Rates, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - American Record and Allied Record with March 24, 1939, Helio Kennedy Letter to James Matles, 1.
      - Richman's Metal Building Specialties, 1939; 2.
      - Phelps Dodge, 1939; 3.
      - Fischer, 1939; 4.
    - Local 1421 Fischer Gout Contracts, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Robert Fischer to James Carey, May 26, 1939; 1.
      - Carey to Fischer, July 18, 1939; 2.
      - Fischer to Carey, July 22, 1939; 3.
      - Fischer to James Matles, September 14, 1939; 4.
      - Matles to Fischer, September 21, 1939; 5.
    - Local 1421 Joint Council Finances, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Julius Emspak to Helio Kennedy, September 22, 1939; 1.
      - Kennedy to Emspak, September 25, 1939; 2.
      - Kennedy to Emspak, September 27, 1939; 3.
    - Local 1421 GE Los Angeles Organization, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Vernon Kennedy to S.E. Gates, September 5, 1939; 1.
      - W.R. Burrows to Julius Emspak, September 8, 1939; 2.
      - James Matles to Kennedy, September 12, 1939; 3.
      - Kennedy to Matles, September 28, 1939; 4.
      - Kennedy to Matles, October 26, 1939; 5.
      - Matles to Kennedy, October 28, 1939; 6.
      - Kennedy to Matles, November 1, 1939; 7.
      - Matles to Kennedy, November 7, 1939; 8.
      - Kennedy to Gates, November 9, 1939; 9.
      - Kennedy to Matles, November 15, 1939; 10.
      - Kennedy to Matles with Memo of Agreement, November 21, 1939; 11.
    - Local 1421 GE Incentive and Job Classification, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - S.E. Gates to Leo Turner, January 10, 1940; 1.
      - Michael Weiss to James Matles, March 1940; 2.
      - Weiss to Matles, March 1940; 3.
      - Ratings, March 1940; 4.
      - Weiss to Matles, March 1940; 5.
      - Proposed Leaflet, March 1940; 6.
      - Wage Classification, March 1940; 7.
      - Charts, March 1940; 8.
      - Shop Committee and GE Meeting Minutes, March 25, 1940; 9.
      - Turner to Gates, March 1940; 10.
      - Julius Emspak to W.R. Burrows with Employee Biographies, April 13, 1940; 11.
      - E.E. Valk to G.H. Pfeif with Employee Biographies, May 9, 1940; 12.
      - Shop Committee and GE Meeting Minutes, July 1940; 13.
      - Burrows to Emspak, July 15, 1940; 14.
    - Local 1421 Coal Mining, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Albert Bliss to James Carey, October 2, 1940; 1.
      - Carey to Bliss, October 17, 1940; 2.
    - Local 1421 Columbia Recording Strike, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - William Elconin to James Matles, March 27, 1941; 1.
      - Elconin to Matles, March 28, 1941; 2.
      - Matles to Elconin, March 31, 1941; 3.
      - Elconin to Matles, April 12, 1941; 4.
      - Expulsions, June 3, 1941; 5.
    - Local 1421 GE Supply Organization, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - William Elconin to James Matles, May 22, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Elconin, June 16, 1941; 2.
      - Elconin to Emspak, June 1941; 3.
    - Local 1421 U.S. Flourescent Lighting Organization, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Carl Brant to Julius Emspak, July 25, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Brant, August 6, 1941; 2.
    - Local 1421 Canon Electric Manufacturing Strike, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - A.L. Wirin to Leo Turner, February 20, 1942; 1.
      - Turner to Julius Emspak, February 23, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Turner, March 23, 1942; 3.
      - Leo Gallagher to Emspak, October 1, 1942; 4.
    - Local 1421 GE Service Grievance, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - William Elconin to Julius Emspak, April 23, 1942; 1.
      - Leo Turner to Emspak, October 15, 1942; 2.
      - Turner to H.A. Simpson, October 15, 1942; 3.
    - Local 1421 Overtime, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Leo Turner to James Matles, December 5, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Turner, December 28, 1942; 2.
      - Turner to Emspak, December 25, 1942; 3.
    - Local 1421 GE Ontario Negotiations, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - George Dodson to Julius Emspak, May 18, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Dodson, May 26, 1943; 2.
    - Local 1421 Maintenance of Membership, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Joseph Dermody to Leo Jandreau, May 5, 1944; 1.
      - Jandreau to Dermody, May 8, 1944; 2.
    - Local 1421 US Electric Motors Strike, 1945-46 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Carl Brant to James Matles, October 28, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Brant, November 1, 1945; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, November 1945; 3.
      - Report of Strike, January 10, 1946; 4.
      - Brant to Matles, January 11, 1946; 5.
    - Local 1421 Peerless Electric Products Strike, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Report of Strike, January 10, 1946; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, April 1, 1946; 2.
    - Local 1421 Capitol Records Strike, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Julius Emspak to Al Stearn, August 26, 1947; 1.
      - Memo, August 1947; 2.
      - Union Proposal, August 18, 1947; 3.
    - Local 1421 Mullenbach Electric Strike, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Report of Strike, June 1, 1948; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, August 24, 1948; 2.
      - Carl Brant to All Stewards, August 26, 1948; 3.
    - Local 1421 Sterling Electric Motors Strike, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - Report of Strike, June 2, 1948; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, August 23, 1948; 2.
    - Local 1421 Morris Metal Negotiations, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Letter to Morris Metal Products, February 7, 1949; 1.
      - William Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald, February 19, 1949; 2.
    - Local 1421 Square D Negotiations, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to William Elconin, March 22, 1950; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to John Gojack, March 22, 1950; 2.
    - Local 1421 Pryne Strike, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Lou Torre to James Matles, June 29, 1951; 1.
      - Report of Strike, July 2, 1951; 2.
      - Ed Laughly to Pryne Strike Families, July 3, 1951; 3.
      - William Elconin to Julius Emspak, July 16, 1951; 4.
      - Elconin to Emspak, July 30, 1951; 5.
      - Matles to Elconin, August 1, 1951; 6.
      - Torre to Matles, August 20, 1951; 7.
      - Matles to Elconin, August 20, 1951; 8.
      - Torre to Matles, August 24, 1951; 9.
      - Emspak to Elconin, October 2, 1951; 10.
    - Local 1421 Johnson Expulsion, 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - James Johnson to General Executive Board, September 29, 1952; 1.
      - Secretary of Julius Emspak to William Elconin, December 8, 1952; 2.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Vernon Brashear, December 18, 1952; 3.
      - Fitzgerald to Elconin, December 18, 1952; 4.
      - Fitzgerald to Elconin, March 11, 1953; 5.
      - Brashear to General Executive Board, March 14, 1953; 6.
      - Emspak to Johnson, April 20, 1953; 7.
    - Local 1421 Dura Steel Strike, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - William Elconin to Julius Emspak, February 1, 1954; 1.
      - Emspak to All UE Locals, February 8, 1954; 2.
      - James Matles to Elconin, February 16, 1954; 3.
      - Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald, February 19, 1954; 4.
      - Press Release, March 1, 1954; 5.
      - Clara Fiering to Matles, April 2, 1954; 6.
      - Fiering to Emspak, April 16, 1954; 7.
      - Fiering to David Ratner, April 20, 1954; 8.
      - Fiering to Matles, May 13, 1954; 9.
      - Fiering to Matles with August 12, 1954, National Labor Relations Board Petition; August 10, 1954, United Auto Workers-American Federation of Labor Letter to NLRB; and August 6, 1954, NLRB Letter to Dura Steel, August 19, 1954; 10.
      - Emspak to Fiering, May 17, 1955; 11.
    - Local 1421 Suspension, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Julius Emspak to Henry Fiering, May 18, 1954; 1.
      - Emspak to Fiering, June 15, 1954; 2.
    - Local 1421 Miscellaneous, 1937-1941 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Vic Levitt to James Matles Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, August 28, 1937; 1.